<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ONAP on Huabing Blog</title>
    <link>https://zhaohuabing.com/tags/onap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ONAP on Huabing Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhaohuabing.com/tags/onap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure ONAP Microservices with Istio Mutual TLS Authentication and RBAC</title>
      <link>https://zhaohuabing.com/post/2018-08-15-manage-onap-with-istio-auth-enabled/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaohuabing.com/post/2018-08-15-manage-onap-with-istio-auth-enabled/</guid>
      <description>In the previous post Manage ONAP Microservices with Istio Service Mesh, we went through the steps of how to install Istio and integrate it with ONAP platform, it’s super simple and has nearly no impact to the existing projects. Now let’s enable Istio auth to secure the inter-service communication inside ONAP, it will need a little bit more efforts, but it’s worth with the benefits brought by it. Installation Download installation scripts from ONAP Gerrit:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage ONAP Microservices with Istio Service Mesh</title>
      <link>https://zhaohuabing.com/post/2018-08-01-manage-onap-with-istio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaohuabing.com/post/2018-08-01-manage-onap-with-istio/</guid>
      <description>In the previous post How service mesh can help during the ONAP Microservice journey, we have discussed why the community wants ONAP to evolve towards Microservice architecture and how service mesh approach could help during the journey. Now it’s time to dip our toe in the water, let’s try out Istio with ONAP by following the below steps. Installation First, download installation scripts from ONAP Gerrit:
git clone https://gerrit.onap.org/r/msb/service-mesh  Kubernetes Master We need Kubernetes 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How service mesh can help during the ONAP Microservice journey</title>
      <link>https://zhaohuabing.com/post/2018-06-22-onap-with-service-mesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaohuabing.com/post/2018-06-22-onap-with-service-mesh/</guid>
      <description>ONAP Beijing is available now!
ONAP, as part of LF Networking, now accounts for more than 65% of global subscriber participation through carriers creating a harmonized, de-facto open source platform. While it&amp;rsquo;s so exciting to see that more operators are deploying ONAP in their commercial network, ONAP community realizes that there are still somewhere we can improve to smooth the deployment process. For example, instead of deploying ONAP as a whole, users may just want to pick some modules, integrate these modules with their existing system to get a customized ONAP solution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>